MARCUS ZAGORSKI

Junior Full Stack Developer

@ marcuszagorski@outlook.com

MarcusZagorski

in marcus-zagorski

J 07511173832

Birmingham, UK

SUMMARY

I'm an individual who's driven by high levels of motivation, and I hold a keen interest in technical growth. I developed an application that highlighted local high scores with a focus on responsive design implementation. Having experience in both front-end and back-end development, allowed me to seamlessly integrate APIs.

EXPERIENCE

Earthing Assistant **ECS Solutions**

May 2020 - April 2021

London, UK

- Ensured all risk-assessments were carried out before completing tasks, leading to a 100% completion of jobs without any injuries, compared to 95% in the previous year
- Assessed any potential risks and reported back to the nominated person (supervisor)
- Collaborated with an authorised person to isolate overhead lines, which ensured the safety of railway workers on-track

Railway Civil Engineer

Stone Alliance Services

March 2018 - February 2020

- West Midlands, UK
- Participated in a team of 6 to complete the stressing and de-stressing of rail lines
- Quickly adapted to learning new machinery such as a Chembre, which led to a 20% increase of speed in completing tasks
- Liaised with supervisors to ensure tasks were completed to the companies standards

Railway Engineer

Carillion PLC

☐ January 2017 - January 2018



- Collaborated with my team members to work additional hours during the holiday season, ensuring timely completion of our project prior to the new year. This collective effort resulted in all project milestones were met
- Gained extensive experience in a variety of groundwork tasks, such as: trial holes, buried ducting & electrical cable management
- Achieved a 100% success rate in all tasks and received outstanding feedback from management

SKILLS

 JavaScript
 ReactJS
 NodeJS
 PostgreSQL

 Adobe Photoshop
 Figma
 HTML

 CSS
 Git Version Control
 Jest

ACHIEVEMENTS

P

Completed a Full Stack bootcamp

Successfully completed an intense 1 year Full Stack developer bootcamp, which has been a pivotal and lifechanging achievement



Passionate mentor in coding

Throughout Code Your Future I've demonstrated a passion for mentorship, by consistently going above and beyond to support my classmates in their coding journey, flourishing a collaborative and inclusive learning environment



Being a good dad!

Although its not career relevant, my kids are my biggest achievement! They constantly inspire and fuel my drive for success both personally and professionally.



Acquired space in iCentrum

In 2024, I successfully secured dedicated study space at iCentrum for Code Your Future students. iCentrum is a digital tech campus which hosts for 120+ businesses

PROJECTS (CLICK LINKS)

Youtube Video Recommendations

High Scores Table Chat Server

Quote Generator Cakes Co

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer

Code Your Future

April 2023 - April 2024

Secondary School

Barr Beacon School

📋 September 2006 – September 2011